Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Members of the UAE Delegation's Visit to Pakistan
  - From the left: a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, a member of the Pakistani delegation, Ahmad Bin Mohammed Al Masaood, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba speaking to two unidentified men near an airplane., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Gatherings; Ceremonies
  - Members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations gathered for a meal, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (foreground, in Emirati dress)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Waiting staff/Servers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Paintings; Officials; Pakistan
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with two members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Cigarettes; Smoking; Hats; Clocks/Watches; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages
  - Agha Mohammad Yahya Khan delivering a speech, with H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi on the left and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba on the right., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Waiting staff/Servers; Uniforms; Microphones; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Officials; Presidents; Drinks/Beverages; Food; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Paintings; Yahya Khan, Agha Mohammad, 1917-1980
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan viewing the unveiling of a plaque in his honor, including members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegations and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr smoking., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Ceremonies; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations gathered for a meal, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (foreground, in Emirati dress)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Officials; Paintings; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Gatherings
- Members of the UAE Delegation Abroad and in the UAE
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting an unidentified man, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left), H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (middle left), and H.E. Sheikh Mubarak Al Nahyan (middle right) at Sheikh Zayed's Diwan., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref20_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Offices; Gatherings; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A group of three unidentified men sitting in ornate chairs in Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan's office., Circa 1974-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.8 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Furnishings; United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Royalty
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the background (wearing ghutra)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000003_000001; Badr, Mohammed (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints 13.8 x 18.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Crowds; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Factories; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Workers; Machines; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Unknown Locations; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - The UAE delegation arriving to a country, including H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (second from the right), H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed (front wearing sunglasses), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.2 x 19.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Unknown Locations; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Hats
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour overseas, with H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi (in military uniform), H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (fourth from the right), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) in the background (likely to be in Pakistan)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.7 x 19.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations; Factories; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gatherings; Officials; Machines; Presidents; Royalty; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front) with a group of men who worked under H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan at a delegation meeting in Pakistan., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref20_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Tents; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Royalty
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front) with a group of men who worked under H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan at a delegation meeting in Pakistan., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref20_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Pakistan; Political Leadership; Royalty
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with a member of a foreign delegation., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) talking with members of a foreign delegation., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Unknown Locations; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Cigarettes; Smoking; Gatherings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) talking with members of a foreign delegation., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Smoking; Officials; Unknown Locations
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with an unidentified man., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations; Officials; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Women; Jewelry; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Bags/Purses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a member of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - Members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations at a gathering for the UAE delegation's arrival to Pakistan, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (middle, sitting)., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Carpets/Rugs; Officials; Pakistan; Presidents; Royalty; Hats; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with three members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Drinks/Beverages
  - Members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegations at a gathering, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from right) and H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem (right)., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Bags/Purses; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Officials; Gatherings; Drinks/Beverages
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour overseas, with H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi (in military uniform), H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (left, behind Sheikh Zayed), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from the right) in the background (likely to be in Pakistan)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Unknown Locations; Factories; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Gatherings; Crowds; Machines; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Members of the UAE Delegation Abroad and in the UAE
  - From the left, in front: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and Ma'ouf Mohammed Al Amri during a visit to Pakistan., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref21_000001_000001; Eveready Studio, (Karachi, Pakistan); 1 Photographic Prints 11.8 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Chandeliers; Gatherings; Guns; Weapons; Medals/Insignia; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) having tea with a member of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref21_000002_000001; Eveready Studio, (Karachi, Pakistan); 1 Photographic Prints 12.4 x 14.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Pakistan; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (middle) reviewing documents with members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref21_000003_000001; Eveready Studio, (Karachi, Pakistan); 1 Photographic Prints 11.8 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Officials; Chandeliers; Hats; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front) exiting an airplane into a crowd., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000004_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Crowds; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) and members of the Emirati delegation arriving to a country overseas., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000005_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation; Officials; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - From the left, with faces visible: H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan speaking to members of a delegation., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.3 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A group of Emirati men and children watching a military show with Edward Hayes, including H.H. Sheikh Khalifa Bin Zayed Al Nahyan (right), H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Khalifa Bin Zayed Al Nahyan (second from the right), Abdullah Al Tahi (left), H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (second from the left, face partially obscured), H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (next to Al Suwaidi), H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (middle), H.H. Sheikh Hazza Bin Zayed Al Nahyan (boy, right and behind Sheikh Zayed), H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Zayed Al Nahyan (boy, left of Sheikh Zayed), H.H. Sheikh Saif Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (between the two boys), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (foreground)., 4 April 1969; AD_MC_093_ref21_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.3 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Boys; Children; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Crowds; Carpets/Rugs; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1965-; Sheikh, Hamdan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, 1963-; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Officials at a gathering, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) and H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki (right)., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000008_000001; Badr, Mohammed (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints 14.3 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Unknown Locations; Food; Furnishings; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) with two unidentified men at Qasr Al Hosn., Circa 1974-1975; AD_MC_093_ref21_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.3 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Forts/Castles; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gardens; Buildings; Architecture
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Saif Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Dawood Al Siksik, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr touring municipality projects., Circa 1970-1973; AD_MC_093_ref21_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.3 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Street Lamps; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A group portrait of members of the Emirati and Iraqi delegations, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left, second row), H.E. Abdullah Bin Ahmad Al Otaiba (fourth from the left, second row), H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (middle, second row), Abdullah Al Thahi (second from the right, second row), Dawood Al Siksik (right, second row), H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (right, first row), and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (third from the left, first row), Ahmed Hassan Al-Bakr (right of Sheikh Zayed), Salah Mehedi Amaj, and Herdan Al Takriti (military suit, front)., 24 July 1969; AD_MC_093_ref21_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.5 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Iraq; Furnishings; Officials; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) looking at a note., Circa 1973-1974; AD_MC_093_ref21_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, H.E. Zaki Nusseibeh, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and Nabel Fateh Albab (standing, left) at one of the pre-unification talks., 1972; AD_MC_093_ref21_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Unknown Locations; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gatherings; Politics; Government; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Books; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Political Leadership; Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1945-2021; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and H.H. Sheikh Hamad Bin Mohammed Al Sharqi during an infrastructure-related visit to Fujairah., Circa 1972-1973; AD_MC_093_ref21_000014_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Men; Group Portraits; Presidents; Royalty; Fujairah, United Arab Emirates; Flags; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.E. Khalifa Juma Al Nabooda, and an unidentified man at an event., Circa 1970-1973; AD_MC_093_ref21_000015_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Newspapers/Magazines; Cigarettes; Smoking; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan holding a plant next to Jafaar Nimeiri, with H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan., Circa 1969-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000016_000001; Office of Media and Culture, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Uniforms; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Medals/Insignia; Ceremonies; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the right: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and an unidentified man having a conversation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref21_000017_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Unknown Locations; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) holding a cane and speaking to H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left), with H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum (obscured by Sheikh Zayed), H.H. Sheikh Suroor Bin Mohammed Bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, H.E. Hamoodah Bin Hamoodah, and H.H. Sheikh Sultan Bin Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (in a row starting from Sheikh Rashid)., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref21_000018_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Gatherings; Group Portraits; Canes/Walking Sticks; Facial Hair; United Arab Emirates; Furnishings; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) walking through a doorway., Circa 1974-1975; AD_MC_093_ref21_000019_000001; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004